{
    "categories": [],
    "description": " Name these actors who starred in recurring roles.",
    "difficulty": -1,
    "questions": [{
        "answer": "Harrison Ford",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "Indiana Jones - 4, 1981-2008"
    }, {
        "answer": "Hugh Jackman",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "Wolverine - 8, 2000-2016"
    }, {
        "answer": "Robert Downey Jr.",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "Iron Man - 7, 2008-2016"
    }, {
        "answer": "Sean Connery",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "James Bond - 7, 1962-1983"
    }, {
        "answer": "Sylvester Stallone",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "John Rambo - 5, 1982-2015"
    }, {
        "answer": "Emma Watson",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "Hermione Granger - 8, 2001-2011"
    }, {
        "answer": "Tobey Maguire",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "Spider-man - 3, 2002-2007"
    }, {
        "answer": "Clint Eastwood",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "\"Dirty\" Harry Callahan - 5, 1971-1988"
    }, {
        "answer": "Roger Moore",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "James Bond - 7, 1973-1985"
    }, {
        "answer": "Christopher Reeve",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "Superman - 4, 1978-1987"
    }, {
        "answer": "Leonard Nimoy",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "Mr. Spock - 8, 1979-2013"
    }, {
        "answer": "Ian McKellen",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "Gandalf - 6, 2001-2014"
    }, {
        "answer": "William Shatner",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "James T Kirk - 7, 1979-1994"
    }, {
        "answer": "Samuel L. Jackson",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "Nick Fury - 7, 2008-2015"
    }, {
        "answer": "Judi Dench",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "M - 7, 1995-2012"
    }, {
        "answer": "Chevy Chase",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "Clark Griswold - 6, 1983-2015"
    }, {
        "answer": "Tyler Perry",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "Mabel \"Madea\" Simmons - 9, 2005-2014"
    }, {
        "answer": "Vin Diesel",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "Dominic Toretto - 6, 2001-2015"
    }, {
        "answer": "Eugene Levy",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "Noah Levenstein (Jim's dad) - 8, 1999-2012"
    }, {
        "answer": "Anthony Daniels",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "C3PO - 7, 1977-2015"
    }, {
        "answer": "Patrick Stewart",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "Proffessor Xavier, 2000-2015"
    }, {
        "answer": "Arnold Schwarzenegger",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "The Terminator, 1984-2015"
    }, {
        "answer": "Mel Gibson",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "Mad Max, 1979-1985"
    }, {
        "answer": "Alan Rickman",
        "category": "Actors by Recurring Role",
        "question": "Severus Snape, 2001-2011"
    }],
    "quizLength": 24,
    "title": "Actors by Recurring Role",
    "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/user-quizzes/30947/actors-by-recurring-role"
}